(The Man Has Come)
- Nice to see you, everyone. - Nice to see you.
- It's been a while, Kai. - Nice to see you all.
- It's great to be back. - My gosh. Yes.
You're here for the man of the hour today.
That's right. I've always wanted to meet him.
I also wanted to congratulate him from the bottom of my heart.
- Congratulate him? - It's the most prestigious...
awards ceremony in the American theater and musical world.
It's none other than the Tony Awards ceremony.
- Tony? - Tony Awards.
His musical won six awards at the ceremony.
He's the first Korean writer to receive such honors.
His musical is sold out for every showing on Broadway...
even as we speak.
He's the writer of the musical, "Maybe Happy Ending."
I'd like to invite in Hue Park. Please come on out!
(Welcome, New Member Hue Park.)
- Hello. - It's Hue Park.
("Maybe Happy Ending")
("Il Tenore")
("Ghost Bakery")
(He's been writing prominent musicals since 2012.)
(The world-class creator)
(Hue Park)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - My gosh.
All right.
Please say hello to our viewers.
Hello, I'm a musical writer,
a lyricist, and a director.
My name is Hue Park. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Hue Park.
- We call them the EGOT. - Right.
- A Korean singer won a Grammy. - Yes.
- Right. - Jo Sumi won the award.
- That's right. - And the Emmy Award too.
Director Hwang Dong Hyuk of "Squid Game."
- That's right. - Bong Joon Ho won an Oscar.
- Right. - With "Parasite."
- He won it with "Parasite." - Yes.
No Korean has ever won a Tony Award.
Thanks to your Tony Award,
Korea became the only non-English speaking country that...
won an award from all four major performing arts awards.
Gosh, really?
Is it like Messi winning the World Cup?
- Let's give it up for him. - Gosh.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
- Gosh. - Congratulations.
Is that why you two are dressed all formally?
- We're copying his fashion style. - What?
- Your outfit... - You look like a parent...
- at your child's recital. - With your shirt and all...
No, you look very stylish.
It looks like you're going to a ball.
You remind me of a scene from "The Phantom of the Opera."
- You remind me of that scene. - I wish not to talk to you guys.
You wish not to talk to us?
- He can't even articulate now. - Listen.
He's embarrassing us.
- Have you watched his musical? - He can't even speak now.
I went to the premiere.
- Really? - You did?
- You did? - Yes.
(Smiling shyly)
You received such a distinguished award.
- I'm sure... - Right.
You must've gotten many offers to join other TV shows.
Could you tell us why you chose our show?
The day after receiving the Tony Award,
I checked my Instagram page.
I had already gotten a direct message.
Immediately after the ceremony?
- So we were the first one to ask? - Gosh.
- Gosh, they're so fast. - I checked them in order.
- That's amazing. - I bet they pulled an all-nighter.
Don't star on other shows.
- Just star on ours. - Right.
- We'll go to New York for you. - Of course.
(The Greatest Showman)
(Times Square in New York)
New York.
(I Live Alone presents...)
(Hue Park, )
(Jun Hyun Moo, Park Na Rae, Kian84, CODE KUNST, KEY, )
(and Kai.)
- It's like a scene from a movie. - His clip surely looks different.
I've been living alone for 18 years now.
I'm Writer Hue Park.
I currently reside in New York, United States.
(New York)
- Yes. - Times Square.
Broadway.
(It's the mecca of plays and musicals.)
(It's a world-leading center of culture.)
- Gosh, "KPop Demon Hunters." - "Soda Pop."
My goodness.
I used to live with my family when I was in Korea.
Then I came to New York for my studies.
It's almost been 18 years.
I've lived here for almost half my life.
I think New York is part of my identity now.
So you weren't young when you went abroad.
Right. I never had an early education abroad either.
I went to New York for my studies at the age of 25.
I thought he was younger than me.
But he's two years older than me.
I'm 42 years old.
- You're older than Na Rae? - Yes.
Yes. What?
She's so beautiful.
- I was surprised when I walked in. - Well...
(Glancing)
Given your outfit, you look like the Tony Award winner.
(Given your outfit, you look like the Tony Award winner.)
I used to be a fan of Tony, the singer.
- Tony An? - Yes.
Okay.
(Current time, 6pm)
It's odd, but when I'm in New York, I find myself walking fast.
That place looks familiar.
- You represent New York, don't you? - That's right.
I guess there are many Korean residents in New York.
(There are many Korean residents in New York besides me.)
(Smug)
- You were there for a few days. - Right.
- But... - Come on.
He ran a marathon there. So it counts as residency.
I think of it as my home.
Him and his cultural toadyism.
(He's Asian just like me.)
- He's a New Yorker. That's cool. - Right.
The city looks so fancy.
How come the city looks different from when Kian84 was there?
(It's obvious that he's a tourist.)
- The city looks the same. - It does look the same.
(The New Yorker only looks ahead while walking.)
(Crowded)
(Glancing)
(He keeps on walking without stopping.)
They're waiting for his musical.
I guess he's going to work now.
It's the musical I worked on as a writer.
It's the theater where "Maybe Happy Ending" will be staged.
"Hue Park."
It's Belasco Theater located on Broadway.
The building has been there for over a century.
- This theater, Belasco Theater, - A century.
Is a landmark of the city.
(Amid the galaxy of many other Broadway musicals...)
I want to watch all of them.
(Standing with a presence)
- Is that a line? - A line?
That's 30 minutes before the show.
The line is long enough to circle around a block.
A lot of people line up in advance.
That's why he seemed proud.
(He walks past the audience waiting in line.)
Hey, Brian.
(He enters through the side gate.)
Gosh, he's entering through the side gate.
- That's cooler. - We call that the stage door.
The crew and cast can only access this door.
(Only authorized personnel can use this door.)
I can feel the long history of this building.
And it makes the theater...
- more romantic. - That's right.
- Hey. - How is it going?
(He goes through the stage door.)
There's backstage past the stage door.
It's the back of the stage.
The dressing rooms of the cast are all there.
Gosh, this is so cool.
And there's also a room...
where stage directors announce their calls.
- That's how it looks. - That's where they give signals.
There's also an area...
where creators like me and the crew could stay and watch.
(He's right at the forefront of a Broadway show.)
Welcome back.
From what I've heard,
writers don't come to every show.
But is it different on Broadway?
Everyone including the writers must be at the theater...
until the musical enters a stable phase.
When a new actor or actress joins, writers come to the theater,
practice with them, and help stabilize the show.
Then who decides if your show is entering a stable phase?
It's more...
- of an implicit understanding. - So it's like a rough evaluation?
I wouldn't say, "rough."
Do you think they wouldn't make an effort?
(Embarrassed)
- He looks so small before fame. - You think they'd wing it?
- Good to see you. - Good to see you.
- Yes. - Good to see you.
Good to see you, Hue.
(He gives his colleagues a hug as soon as he comes to work.)
- He's giving everyone a hug. - Just like that?
- My gosh. Hey, you. - I know.
Don't make me emotional.
(Choking up)
We've been working together for almost a year.
So when I see them,
I feel like I'm home.
(Hue goes off somewhere after greeting his colleagues.)
The building looks so classic.
(He follows the voices of the people.)
(The theater is packed with the audience.)
My gosh. It's a full house.
Lately, our ticket sales have hit over 100 percent...
which I'm grateful for.
We even sold out all the standing-room-only tickets.
Our sales have been at 103 percent from what I've heard.
What do you mean by 103 percent?
It's like standing on a train...
- without a seat. - That's right.
- You can do that? - I see.
- How many seats are there? - About 1,000 seats.
How much is one ticket?
(If you don't mind me asking...)
The most expensive seat costs 500 dollars.
- That's 700,000 won. - That's expensive.
But on average, our tickets cost about 200 dollars.
So that's a little short of 300,000 won.
That's for a regular seat?
Is there a friends and family discount?
There are no friends and family discounts.
It's a cold business model.
The ticket system for Broadway shows...
- is different from ours. - How?
As for popular shows like this one,
- the ticket prices can go up. - There's an added premium?
- Right. - There's no ceiling for the prices.
Looking at the number of the sold tickets,
the production can increase the prices.
- So it's like a market price? - Yes, it is.
That's right. It's based on the market.
- It's a capitalistic society. - Of course.
- It's the ultimate capitalism. - Gosh.
If you want to watch it so badly, pay up.
- Hi. - Hey, Hue.
I'm going to be standing right here. Yes.
All right. Perfect. Thanks.
There weren't any seats left for me either.
So I just watched it standing in the back.
But that's cooler.
It's called the Writer's Alley.
- It's an alley for the writers. - Writer's Alley.
Writers can watch the show...
all the way in the back of the theater...
while looking at the backs of people's heads.
- You can check their reaction. - To watch their reaction.
Yes. So it's a bit nerve-racking.
I can clearly see their unadulterated reaction.
- Right. - It's like immediate feedback.
- Yes. That's right. - Right.
- You must be nervous. - That's a nerve-racking moment.
(Glancing)
(Chattering)
- They must be his fans. - They recognized him.
I'm sorry.
- Are you the writer of the show? - Yes, I am.
- Oh, my gosh. - Gosh, that's very cool.
We're so honored to stand by you.
I'm watching it for the second time.
- Really? Thank you so much. - Yes. They already watched it.
We waited in line for four hours today.
- Oh, my gosh. - Yes.
Yes. That's making me emotional.
That's amazing.
Enjoy the show. Thanks for coming.
("Maybe Happy Ending")
(In no time, it gets quiet in the theater.)
(Grabbing)
Copy, 55 seconds.
(Fidgeting)
Actually, I get nervous every time I watch the show.
"What if the audience today doesn't like the show?"
It comes with the job.
There have been hundreds of showings so far.
Including its performances in Korea,
the musical has been running for ten years.
But my palms get so sweaty when I watch the show.
You get nervous every time?
Strangely, yes. I can never seem...
- to get used to it. - Really?
No matter how many times I watch it, I'll always get nervous.
You never know what might happen on stage.
- Right. - It's a live performance.
- The cast's energy differs daily. - Right.
Gosh, I'm getting nervous for them.
Thank you so much.
(The last inspection before the show is complete.)
Go.
(The lights go out as she gives a green light.)
Oliver.
(The musical finally begins.)
(The audience welcomes him with a round of applause.)
- The vibe has a sense of freedom. - I love that!
(Glancing)
(Seoul, Korea)
Oh, it's written in Korean.
Since Korea is the setting, there are Korean subtitles too.
Mi Do.
(Korean characters are seen throughout the musical.)
I'll have to model it for you later, Hwaboon.
- Hwaboon. - Hwaboon.
(He says the word, "flowerpot," in Korean.)
We considered Hwaboon as one of our characters.
So we transliterated it into Korean.
And they loved it.
They even gave a separate dressing room for it.
- The flowerpot? - A dressing room for a flowerpot?
Seeing Korean on the screen...
- makes me feel so proud. - Right.
- I feel a sense of patriotism. - Yes.
Having Korean characters makes things hip these days.
Why would you focus on that?
(This hip musical is a story about AI robots.)
Gosh, everyone is laughing.
(Relieved)
(The audience continues to laugh.)
Hearing them laugh makes me feel good.
(Responsive)
The atmosphere is nice.
(Relieved)
(The night deepens, fueled by the audience's energy.)
The Five Series runs out of battery really quickly.
(In no time, they're performing the final number.)
We at least need the Five Series. It's a fashionable design.
The charger is losing...
He's getting misty-eyed.
Their acting was particularly good that day.
I was impressed by their acting.
So I was moved by the show even more than usual.
I hope so.
(The show comes to an end with a surge of heartfelt emotions.)
(Applause)
(Everyone in the audience gives them a standing ovation...)
(during the curtain call.)
(Amazed)
There's a standing ovation.
(They're touched too.)
(Choking up)
It's a tearjerker.
(The applause goes on without end.)
(The show ends to thunderous applause.)
(Cheering)
(Surprised)
- You're tearing up. - He's tearing up.
These feelings are difficult to describe in words.
It feels like my heart reached them.
In my opinion, a show requires a little bit of luck...
and hard work of many people...
in every role.
And that's a rare probability.
So it made me emotional.
(So it made me emotional.)
I believe the applause at the end is also meant...
for the hard-working crew.
When I think of all the hard work they did,
I get even more emotional.
(Hue leaves after the show.)
(Lingering feelings)
- Hey. - Hi.
(He heads somewhere while still feeling emotional.)
- Yes! - Hey, I cried.
- Yes. We did it. - I want to know...
- We did it. - We did it.
- Gosh, that was crazy. Yes. - Great.
Gosh, he must feel great.
(Feeling liberated)
How much longer will the show go on?
- It's an open run. - Is it?
There's no set closing date.
The show will continue to run as long as people keep coming...
to our show. That's the system.
For now, tickets are available until early next year.
There's no predetermined closing date.
Not every show has this privilege.
- Of course, not. - Right.
- Some shows must close early on. - Right.
Hi, Hue.
Oh, my gosh.
- Hey. - Hey, Hue.
Where were you watching from?
From the back, yes.
- What? - You made me emotional.
Yes. That's the goal.
I liked what you did.
"Okay, goodbye." And then...
You did something like that today. And that was funny.
- Right, exactly. Yes. - Yes. That was a joke.
- Well, you were fantastic. - The atmosphere looks good.
She improvised and did a new sound effect.
She wanted to know if it worked or not.
So I told her it was funny.
Don't party too hard without us.
- That's the male lead. - It's just in the house.
It's the perfect day to look out the window.
(He won the Best Performance by a Leading Actor.)
Yes. I knew he looked familiar.
- It was a great show. Really. - Yes. Thanks a lot.
I mean, this literally happened.
This guy from the audience who was standing next to me said,
"This is my second time."
They came here at 6am...
- Just to catch the show? - to watch...
- To watch the show again. - Hopefully, it was a good show.
I hope we did okay.
I mean, even that made me super emotional.
- How she was so engaged... - Yes.
With the work...
Let me give you a big hug.
- I just love and adore you. - All right.
I'm so grateful for you. I'll miss you, man.
- Yes. - Did you like the show?
- Yes. It was great. - It was a good show.
It was a pretty good show.
- We did good on it. - I'm joking. Yes.
It was a great show.
- It made me emotional. Good job. - Yes.
"Emotional." He uses that word a lot.
- I use it to say I'm touched... - You're moved.
And moved. That's when I use that word.
But it might have to do...
- with the plot of our show. - What?
A lot of the cast members and the audience use that word.
Here's the thing. Certain shows deplete your energy afterward.
But some shows actually give you more energy...
- even after performing for hours. - Right.
"Maybe Happy Ending" must give more energy to people afterward.
(The emotional musical comes to an end.)
(A crowd has formed in front of the theater.)
- Why are there so many people? - What?
- They're waiting for the cast. - To see them get off work?
- My gosh. - I didn't know...
this culture existed there too.
My gosh.
They're so kind.
(Grabbing)
(Hue quietly gets off work by himself.)
I usually run away from the crowd quietly.
When they stop me there, I feel so awkward.
I usually run out of there fast with my hat on.
That's how an artist ought to be.
(Chuckling)
(Smirking)
- What do you mean? - But I became an attention-seeker.
"How come there's no one here?" Like this?
- Yes. - He held a solo exhibit...
in Seongsu-dong.
He was so self-conscious around people.
He showed up in front of them...
on his way to work, after work, and during his breaks.
You stood there for a long time too.
"How come they can't recognize me?"
- He's so self-aware. Yes. - Right, he is.
(He's so self-aware.)
(Hue quickly gets off work.)
- That's cool. - My gosh.
He's trudging back home after a successful show.
(He enters a nearby subway station.)
He's taking the subway home.
(He hurriedly passes through the turnstile.)
(A New York subway train enters the platform in no time.)
(I must hurry back home.)
(Opening)
(He opens up a book as soon as he sits down.)
(Hue is instantly engrossed in the book.)
- How long does it take to get home? - About 15 minutes.
That's pretty close.
The rent must be quite expensive.
The rent in my neighborhood is quite reasonable.
The next stop is 52nd Street.
(Getting up)
(Rushing)
It's quiet.
(Unlike Broadway, his neighborhood is quiet.)
The vibe changed completely.
- It reminds me of Seongsu-dong. - Yes.
It's a quiet residential area.
So there are rarely people out on the street at night.
(He lives in Queens, 15 minutes away from Broadway.)
I see. He lives in Queens.
That's where Spider-Man lives.
(When he walks down an alley on the outskirts of New York City, )
(he arrives at his sweet home right away.)
(Creaking)
This building is 100 years old.
I live on the fourth floor which is the top floor.
- Without the elevator? - There's no elevator.
(The building has no elevator, )
(and he must use a key to open it like the old-fashioned way.)
That's how it is in the US.
They still use those old-school keys.
Alexa.
Turn on all the Hue lights.
- What? - Do you have a roommate?
Alexa is AI.
AI?
He's using AI right after we said he used an old-school key.
(There's a smart home within an old building.)
(Flinging open)
(He stays busy as soon as he arrives.)
(Gushing)
(He fills up the pot with water and puts it on the stove.)
That's when you get hungry.
I do that as soon as I come home.
(Let me see.)
- What? - Gosh.
- The rustling sound means ramyeon. - That's a bag of ramyeon.
- It's Neoguri. - Neoguri.
(Neoguri Ramyeon)
That's the US version of it.
(His favorite after-work snack is ramyeon.)
- You sometimes crave it. - Right.
- You crave it. - Yes.
Here's what musical actors and actresses do.
Let's say Act One just ended.
This is what we talk about during the intermission.
"Hey, what will you get today?"
- "What kind of food?" - Right.
- We talk about food a lot. - I see. After the show?
Hyun Moo actually eats food instead of talking about it.
Why think about it?
Use that time to have one more bite.
(Rustling)
What's that?
(Seaweed?)
(He adds seaweed to the water, meant for the ramyeon.)
It doesn't come with the kelp.
So I started adding seaweed to it.
- Oh, my gosh. - Why?
Then it's not real Neoguri.
- That's not right. - Right.
(The US version has different ingredients from the original one.)
The US version doesn't have kelp.
(This news had gone viral a while ago.)
My gosh, this is...
But that must be such a disappointment.
I was so disappointed at first.
I was very flustered when I first came here 18 years ago.
I thought it was a defective product initially.
So I bought another one, but it was the same.
That's why I add seaweed to it.
I thought it was someone's birthday.
He added a lot too.
That's enough for a mom who just gave birth.
(He adds every particle of the spicy seasoning.)
(He recreates the flavor from home.)
What about kimchi?
He has it.
(Kimchi completes the dish.)
- He's Korean, you know? - This proves he's Korean indeed.
- Right. - He needs kimchi, of course.
(It's ready.)
(He quickly sets the table, so the noodles don't get soggy.)
(Even the color looks authentic.)
It looks tasty.
Neoguri with seaweed looks pretty good.
(A meal of a Korean guy in New York)
(Let's eat now.)
(Stirring)
(Cooling)
(Slurping)
That looks good.
(Yes, this is it!)
That hits the spot.
Having ramyeon after the show hits the spot.
(The taste of Korea fills his hungry stomach after the show.)
(Captivated)
(This is so good.)
(Staring)
You need a funny video to watch while eating.
(Chuckling)
- Isn't that us? - That's Na Rae's laugh.
What?
Mr. Ahn wrote a comment right away.
- My goodness. - "Can you travel..."
- "for work?" - That's me!
People watch me abroad!
- The broom-to-be. - The broom-to-be.
(He's getting into it.)
(Na Rae is enjoying her life.)
That's the camouflage cream.
(Chuckling)
(Giggling)
After the show, I come home at night...
and eat ramyeon.
I watch Korean variety shows too.
At least in that moment,
doing that alleviates my stress.
It's fleeting, though.
(Nothing is stressing him out while watching Na Rae's day.)
I'm not sure. I have to see it through to know.
My gosh, he finished everything.
(He keeps watching it in the living room and enjoys it.)
(Laughing)
I really enjoyed that episode.
- That's... The broom-to-be. - The broom-to-be is in New York.
(The seaweed-wrapped broom-to-be has followed him to New York.)
We have to watch that again?
I kept watching that while having seaweed.
Dive into Neoguri.
I can't tell from where her dress starts.
(As he laughs with the Rainbow Club members...)
That episode was really funny.
Your broom-to-be episode made him happy.
(Touched)
(His hectic day in New York has ended.)
(Next day)
I'm curious about his morning.
(Hue is still fast asleep.)
(An old-fashioned alarm clock)
That's how an American alarm clock sounds.
What do you mean? An American alarm clock?
(He doesn't even budge.)
(Beeping rapidly)
(The American alarm clock is going off ruthlessly.)
Seriously. It's a traditional alarm sound.
(Beeping rapidly)
Gosh, that's no joke.
(The old-fashioned alarm sound wakes him up.)
I left my smartphone in the living room on purpose.
I started to put only the alarm clock in my bedroom.
- Gosh, that's not easy. - Then...
you don't check your phone before going to sleep?
I'm trying not to do that.
Having my phone in the bedroom distracts me...
- from sleep. - That's right.
When I'm on my phone,
- I struggle to fall asleep. - Right.
(He wakes up at the sound of his clock, not his phone.)
(Grabbing)
A robe.
The American vibe.
"The American vibe?"
(Drawing)
Check out how well-lit his room is.
Since I live on the top floor, my room gets a lot of sunlight.
Since I spend a long time working from home,
I'm sensitive to noise between floors.
(Fumbling)
- Gosh, your face looks so puffy. - Oh, no.
You now have the face of a raccoon.
Gosh, I can't believe it. No way.
They started to pick on him now.
They're teasing him now that he's not at the theater.
(This is so fun.)
(Utterly nervous)
(He goes somewhere after turning into a raccoon.)
(I should wash up briefly.)
(Refreshed)
(He comes back to the bedroom after washing up.)
(Grabbing)
(Pounding)
(He immediately makes the bed.)
(Pulling hard)
(Tight)
- That's how it's done at hotels. - At hotels.
It's an old habit of mine.
Since I work from home,
- You're a neat guy. - I want my house to be tidy.
(Looking neat)
(I'm done.)
It's nice.
The house I live in is located in Queens, New York.
I lived in Brooklyn for many years,
but moved here during COVID-19.
(Welcome to Hue's house.)
It's bigger than I expected.
It's perfect for one person.
In the US, it's called a one-bedroom apartment.
It's a typical apartment with one bedroom.
The living room is at the end.
Tony Awards.
- It's so neat. - It's cozy.
There are a kitchen, a restroom, and a living room.
I think it's a very fitting place for me.
The Brooklyn apartment I lived in for many years...
was a studio apartment.
When I moved here, I got a living room.
I got a bedroom with a door.
When I slept with the door closed,
I felt very successful.
"Now, I can sleep with the door closed."
Those who live in a studio apartment will agree.
It's nice when the space is divided.
Since you've won the Tony Awards,
you should begin looking into properties.
But Tony Awards don't come with a money prize.
I also haven't been paid for Broadway performances yet.
- What? - Why not?
- Hold on. - Payments take a long time.
When will you receive the money?
It's done every quarter of a year.
In the first quarter, the musical didn't make any profits.
Thus, I didn't get paid.
The payments for the 2nd and 3rd quarters...
will be made soon.
Do you go and count the audience members every day?
- Do you calculate the profits? - That's right.
- I bet he takes photos. - Yes.
There's no chance of them not paying you, right?
- It won't happen. - I believe they'll pay me.
- We signed a contract. - That's right.
- All right. - They give me the minimum amount.
Every week, they give me the minimum amount.
I expected better from them,
but New Yorkers didn't uphold their promises.
You must be thinking about the New York-based newspaper.
The New York-based newspaper.
- Because of the newspaper? - He's very angry about it.
If they don't give him his money, let's send Sung Hwan.
I'll go there as a witness.
You just want an excuse to go to New York.
I spend a lot of time at home.
I can't focus if there's too much going on.
I stick to the white and wood tones.
It's like a house you see in a magazine.
There's another plant. Hwaboon.
- Hwaboon. - I'll explain later, Hwaboon.
I have many plants at home.
The house is similar to yesterday's stage.
- You must be sensitive to colors. - That's right.
I graduated from an art university.
- You studied the arts. - Yes.
In Korea, I majored in creative writing.
I went to the US to study the arts.
After majoring in the arts,
I worked at a marketing company as a designer.
Since I was used to writing,
I decided to continue writing my own works.
That was why I began writing at home after work.
My works got turned into musicals in Korea.
Then I became a full-time writer.
How fascinating.
- He's a talented writer. - Yes.
(Hue comes back to the kitchen.)
(He sits at the table.)
(Grabbing)
(He enjoys a cup of fragrant coffee and a book.)
- He reads a lot. - Gosh.
(Gosh, he's cool!)
It shows that he's a writer.
That's the New Yorker's life we dream of.
Had we been in New York, we would've read books.
Of course. I would've read books.
- The sunlight is different. - I would've read every day.
It's a routine of mine.
In the morning, I read a book in Korean.
In the afternoon or at night,
I read a book in English. It became a habit.
How cool.
Ever since I was little,
- I've had a reading addiction. - A reading addiction.
Even in elementary school,
I couldn't go to the restroom without a book.
It was like a condition.
As I get older, I think that this ability is like a muscle.
If you stop reading,
- you keep reading the same part. - That's right.
"What did they say earlier?" I have to go back and check.
You need to keep reading...
to work the muscles in your brain.
I make an effort to be careful.
(Hue's morning routine that protects his brain health...)
(is reading.)
When I look at the smartphone,
I feel like...
- my brain is slowing down. - That's right.
Only the cellphones are becoming smarter.
Yes.
Reading in the morning is great.
(Hue finishes reading to make himself smarter.)
(He rinses the cup he has used right away.)
He cleans up right away.
Do you do the dirty dishes right away?
Yes. There are too many cockroaches in the US.
- I see. - New York is like that.
If I don't clean up,
I get insects in the apartment.
(He does the dirty dishes so that there won't be any insects.)
(Opening)
(Hue takes something out.)
A mat?
- Will he work out at home? - Is it a yoga mat?
Will he work out now?
(He takes off the robe he has been wearing.)
(Plank)
- Plank. - Plank.
For how many minutes will he do it?
(Smiling)
(Heave-ho)
It's embarrassing to call it an at-home workout.
These days, my posture is so bad...
- that my back... - Right. It's for his posture.
And neck hurt.
So it's my goal to exercise even if it's for 15 to 20 minutes.
I don't have much time,
so I do it briefly in the morning.
(A simple exercise after reading is a part of the morning routine.)
(Clenching his jaw)
His legs aren't half bad.
(He moves on to the upper body exercise.)
Back in the day,
I did weightlifting.
- What? - Yes.
(Did Writer Hue Park do weightlifting?)
Back in the day, I did weightlifting.
- What? - Yes.
- I joined a team. - Weightlifting?
He really enjoyed his life.
I wasn't a professional.
I joined a weightlifting team in the neighborhood.
- Was it like a club? - Yes.
(A few years ago, when he was in a weightlifting crew)
- All right. - That's a bit...
- Is that Hue? - Yes. He's good.
- This is unexpected. - Yes.
He has so many different sides.
(He brings out his skills from the past.)
- Nice. - That's...
(Morning strength exercise)
I thought he'd like aerobic exercise.
I don't like aerobic exercise.
You like weightlifting.
(My goodness)
(Panting)
I became tired after ten minutes.
- Did you exercise for ten minutes? - Yes.
I...
(He's exhausted after exercising for 10 minutes.)
(Covered in sweat)
(He rubs a facial cleanser on his face.)
(Then he prepares a washcloth right away.)
What are you doing?
In the US, the bathroom floor is kept dry.
That's why you don't splash water.
That's why I use a washcloth.
- Really? - Yes.
I wet a washcloth in water...
and wipe my face.
Then it keeps the water from splashing on the floor.
That makes sense.
I learned it from my American friends.
(After washing up cleanly, )
(he changes quickly.)
(Taking out)
(He fills his bag with items.)
It's full.
(He puts on a cap.)
(Then he takes a key and goes outside.)
(Let's go.)
(He arrives at the entrance of the 1st floor.)
(Creaking)
(He comes outside as he listens to the sound...)
(that adds to the atmosphere.)
The neighborhood is pretty.
It's nice.
(Hue's welcomed by the peaceful scenery.)
- It's relaxed. - My goodness.
What's that?
(He walks diligently while carrying a big bag.)
Laundry center?
(He arrives at a laundromat.)
I don't have a washing machine at home,
so I need to go to a coin laundromat.
Firstly, there's no space for a washing machine.
And if I need the landlord's permission...
to put a washing machine in the apartment.
- I see. - But...
since the pipes are too old in this 100-year-old building,
I think it'll be impossible to set up a washing machine...
even if I had space for it.
So I visit a laundromat...
once every 2 to 3 weeks.
In the US, having a washing machine at home...
is a luxury.
- Still? - Yes.
If my friend moves to a new place and has a washing machine,
I say, "You've made it big."
(You've made it big, man.)
How fascinating.
Since he won Tony Awards,
I expected him to live in a luxurious house.
If my parents see this,
they'll find me pathetic.
You won Tony Awards.
You'll get paid now.
- That's right. - You'll make a lot of money now.
- You should rake in the money now. - That's right.
Rake it in.
(Today, he's putting dirty laundry into the washing machine instead.)
(Clinking)
(He puts in the coins that match the price.)
(He opens the top to pour in the laundry detergent.)
I need to go back to the theater in the afternoon,
so I must do everything in the morning.
(Feeling much lighter, he comes out of the laundromat.)
(Checking)
Set a timer for 40 minutes.
You divide up the time very well.
I need to go back and take out my laundry.
That makes sense.
(Shall I walk around while my laundry is getting done?)
- He's entering a restaurant. - Let's eat.
Isn't New York famous for its bagels?
It's a cafe that's near my place.
I actually go there almost every morning.
- They sell bagels. - Bagels sound nice.
Hey, how is it going?
Obviously, having fun. What can I get for you today?
Can I have a BLT on an everything bagel?
What else?
Iced matcha latte with skim milk.
- Is it going to be to stay? - Yes, to stay.
Thank you.
(Hue sits outside.)
How nice.
(Taking out)
It's a book.
You're right.
Even the man behind Hue is reading.
There are many writers in the neighborhood.
It's very cool.
(Writing)
The man behind you must dream of becoming Writer Hue Park.
(Chuckling)
- That's right. - He wouldn't even know who I am.
- Still... - Today, Kai is being a bootlicker.
Gosh, don't say that.
How could you call him a bootlicker?
Why would he dream of becoming Writer Hue Park?
- Think about it. - A bootlicker?
Call him a sweet-talker, okay?
(Kai sweet-talked a lot today.)
(Turning his head)
(Listening right away)
(Kai diligently dreamed of standing next to Hue Park.)
I haven't heard that expression in a long time.
Kai is sweet-talking since he might meet you again.
"I heard that you did musicals in Korea as well."
My goodness.
(Moved)
(There's no sweet-talking in the quiet cafe in New York.)
Here you go.
- Thank you so much. - Enjoy.
(New York's bagel sandwich looks tasty.)
Bagel.
(He picks up a piece...)
(and takes a big bite.)
(He holds the book in place with a cellphone.)
(A book in one hand...)
(and a bagel in the other hand)
(This is how a New Yorker eats.)
It looks delicious.
(He enjoys a cool sip of the bittersweet matcha latte.)
Matcha latte is the best.
Matcha latte must be popular over there as well.
- It's a global trend. - It's a major hit in the US.
Really?
As I eat breakfast at the cafe in the morning,
I read books and write scripts.
Many times, I revised the script of "Maybe Happy Ending" there.
I wrote most of the script of "Il Tenore" there.
I wrote most of the script of "Ghost Bakery" there.
- I wrote many scripts there. - It's a precious place.
It's a meaningful place if I think about it.
It's so nice.
Kai's words don't sound innocent anymore.
- It's Hyun Moo's fault. - I mean...
It's Hyun Moo's fault.
"I heard that you were working on a new musical."
(There it goes)
There it goes
That's right.
(The sweet-talker even prepared a serenade!)
He even practiced a number.
I'll get goosebumps if Kai is in his musical this autumn.
But he's a great musical actor.
I feel embarrassed before these precious guests.
(This precious guest is reading in a dignified way.)
It's nice.
It's so nice.
(The warm cafe of the day brings inspiration.)
(Hue reads as he enjoys the relaxing time.)
(Getting up)
(I enjoyed the food.)
Thank you.
(Walking)
(He begins to walk with matcha latte in his hand.)
(Glancing over)
The streets are so pretty.
(He observes whatever he sees on the road.)
(The sweet scenery of the neighborhood)
I enjoy walking.
When I walk down the residential area...
or the streets,
I become attuned to the rhythm of the city.
Then I really feel like I'm getting used to the city.
That's the neighborhood with more houses...
than apartments.
The trees are nice.
(Halting)
(He suddenly stops and checks the map.)
(He resumes walking after checking his location.)
- It's a real estate office. - It's a real estate office.
It's obvious.
- They're the same everywhere. - Of course.
(Advertisements for the properties)
I began to look for a place.
"Until when will I be able to carry around my laundry?"
- I had that thought. - I see.
- There's no elevator. - That's right.
I began to dream of buying a house.
(Where will my house be?)
(Glancing over)
Let's look for a property.
(I'll look them up myself.)
(Oh, my!)
- This one is... - How much is it?
It's 1.22 million dollars.
Is it an apartment? What is it?
It's a 2 or 3-story building. It's a house.
It's sold.
This one is 1.4 million dollars.
(The next property is 1.4 million dollars.)
- It looks nice. - It's sold.
It has four rooms.
It isn't like I can buy it.
(He feels dejected.)
(Let's look around a bit more.)
I don't have the means to move right away.
"If I make a lot of money in the future,"
"I want to live in a house with many trees." With that thought,
I check out the houses whenever I go on a stroll.
I want to plant the trees that need a lot of sunlight.
In winter, I want to put up the Christmas decorations.
Since I'm used to living as an international student,
I've always had an emotional burden of needing...
to move out of the current place at any time.
It's the final goal of someone who has lived in this city...
for many years as an international student.
You should visit "Where Is My Home."
How about our special on filial duty?
- Finding a house? - A special on filial duty.
If I send my mom there, I'll be an unfilial son.
Imagine sending your mom to New York to be a filial son.
My mom should try living in a nice city.
How will she live there with the language barrier?
In the center of the world...
She should try a bagel.
(Mom, Moomoo will let you eat a bagel!)
When will I be able to live in a house like that?
Bye.
(After checking out some houses, he picks up his laundry.)
Since I just came back from checking out the houses,
I couldn't help but think,
"Until when will I need to use a laundromat?"
You had a reality check.
(Sad)
(He goes up the stairs with a heavy bag.)
(Sighing)
(Pouring out)
(He folds the clean clothes as soon as he comes home.)
(He puts them in the drawers right away.)
(Ringing)
(Who is ringing the doorbell?)
(Curious)
Is it a guest? Is it a friend?
- Hello. - Will.
- Will? - Hello.
Hello.
He's a writer and a composer, Will Aronson.
He majored in music at Harvard University...
and studied musical theater at New York University.
He's a friend I've been working with for 14 years.
("Maybe Happy Ending," "Bungee Jumping of Their Own,")
("Il Tenore," "Ghost Bakery")
You get a set amount of time to say the acceptance speech.
They only give you 1 minute and 30 seconds.
- There's a time limit. - Yes.
So many people misunderstand. Because we're always together,
people just assume that we're a couple.
- It's New York. - It's New York.
Is he married?
Yes. Will is happily married.
I felt so victimized...
that I revealed it as a part of the acceptance speech.
(He explained himself during the acceptance speech.)
I had just moved to New York...
and Will had come back after composing a musical in Korea.
There was a mutual friend of ours.
"You wrote lyrics in Korea."
"He's a composer. He composed numbers in Korea."
"Shouldn't the two of you get to know each other?"
That was how we became friends.
It was fate.
(Will and Hue remain best friends and partners.)
I don't know why, but...
- "Will and Hue" go well together. - Right.
"Hue and Will" sounds weird. It's better the other way around.
"Will and Hue" go well together.
They go well together.
They go well together like Dolce and Gabbana.
- Are you joining in as well? - Hold on.
Do you want to be in musicals too?
(The new sweet-talker does his best.)
I have a special delivery.
What is it?
I'm not sure if you would know.
Where can I bring it?
We can go to the living room.
(He follows the Korean way and naturally takes off his shoes.)
Of course, he must follow the Korean way.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Hold on.
He brought that up five floors.
What could it be?
It's food.
- No. - Oh, my gosh!
- "Tony?" - It's the Tony Award.
She just called that food.
(Smiling from ear to ear)
Oh, my gosh.
It's so heavy.
The Tony Award trophy...
had to have my name carved into it.
I sent it back to the organizer.
The trophy was ready and I had to go back to pick it up,
but I was in Seoul.
Will went for me to pick it up...
and he finally brought it to my house.
Was the trophy given to each person?
Yes.
- I see. - That's nice.
Gosh, it's already been two months.
Oh, my gosh!
(He opens it right away.)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Gosh! - How was it?
That's impressive.
It felt weird...
to see my name on it.
Amazing.
You've got two more, so you know,
don't spend too much time.
(Joking)
Here's number two.
You're going to go through all of them?
- I guess so. - That's truly amazing.
- Really nice, isn't it? - Best Original Score.
The last one.
Best Book of a Musical.
I'm getting emotional.
Super emotional.
(Laughing)
Best Book of a Musical.
Best Score.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
This is for the Best Musical.
That's amazing.
It's insane.
Shouldn't they be put into a glass display case?
Kai is about to send one for him.
If only that's possible...
He would send a crystal one.
Would a glass one be enough? It should be a crystal one.
- "Made by Kai." - Right.
Of course.
Yes. Because I think you're going to have these for a long time.
If you ever move apartments, you're going to need these to...
Should I keep these wrappers too?
You have to keep the plastic bags too.
- Of course. - I would keep them.
- I would keep them too. - I would keep them too.
I don't want to throw it out yet.
I'm going to put this in the box.
Okay. Sounds good.
- I couldn't throw it out easily. - Right.
I got some stuff from H-Mart. I don't know if you want it.
Let's take a look.
Well, I got...
Gosh, there's barely anything inside.
Do you not cook at all?
There are times when I do and I don't.
I haven't been cooking these days.
- I got this. - You should feel comfortable...
- Sushi. - to eat it.
I can sit here and have a glass of water.
And...
Ta-da! It's champagne.
- Champagne. - Are we having some of this?
- Yes. - Are you showing it to me?
I've been saving it.
- Oh, great. - To celebrate.
Okay. I can't wait.
Can I help? What do I do?
No. I'll take care of it.
Gosh, that's so cute.
- What? - That surprised me.
I've never seen that.
- What? - What?
- Should it go back in the fridge? - I'm getting goosebumps.
- What? - His Korean is so good.
This is scarier than "The Sixth Sense."
Will's Korean...
is improving day by day at a scary rate.
He's from Harvard.
(I loved you)
- "Southbound Train" by Kim Su Hee? - It's "Southbound Train."
He has Harvard on his face.
Stop speaking nonsense.
You can see pencils on his face.
What are you saying?
Would you like to take this first?
Okay.
Just take this first.
(The man that reminds you of pencils moves the food.)
(The wine glasses are placed too.)
Multi-grain rice...
and braised black beans?
(The celebration meal for the two is ready.)
Gosh, they're having rice and champagne.
All right.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
We made it.
(A sip in honor of the Tony Award)
The two must feel delighted.
I want some rice,
so you should have this.
(Hue moves the sushi closer to Will.)
Won't it be awkward to eat the sushi with a fork?
(There's only one pair of chopsticks.)
You should use these then.
- I only have 1 pair. - You only have 1 pair?
- Right. - You must really live alone.
- His Korean is so good. - His Korean is so good.
Did you have to poke at me where it hurts?
- I'm sorry. - Gosh.
Does it feel weird to eat sushi with a fork?
Right. It's a bit strange.
You've become an Asian now.
So he uses chopsticks.
He's good at using them.
Should we sit on the floor?
Sure.
He does that too?
(Plopping down naturally)
- That's a true Korean. - That's a true Korean.
He's certainly a South Korean foreigner.
Only a Korean would sit on the floor against the couch.
Hue is eating with the fork instead.
I already insisted first that...
sushi must be eaten with chopsticks.
It's really good.
I'm not just being polite.
- That's a relief. - Where find this sushi?
Did you mean, "Where did you find this sushi?"
Right. What did I just say?
"Where find this sushi?"
Where find this sushi?
I must be crazy.
- He's surely a Korean. - Gosh, that's hilarious.
We understand each other even without saying anything.
We can all tell if we are upset.
We can tell if we are happy as well.
We feel like twins.
(The two can tell just by looking each other in the eye.)
It's good.
- Really? - It's different but it's good.
I like multi-grain rice.
(Groaning)
It's too healthy,
so it doesn't taste that good.
I have the taste of a middle-aged man.
I hated beans when I was young.
- What about now? - I like them.
(Laughing)
You have definitely become a middle-aged man.
He's teasing him in Korean.
We always tease each other.
(The middle-aged man persistently eats the beans and rice.)
(Eating)
(Will eats the watermelon.)
It's good.
He's fully equipped with Korean.
He must've been really hungry.
I said that I wasn't hungry.
I said that in case...
- you didn't have any food. - It was a white lie?
Yes. Actually, I was very hungry.
- He's so cute. - He's so cute.
I didn't know if you had food or not,
so I just lied.
- Were you being considerate? - Yes.
In case he felt awkward if there wasn't any food.
(A great meal thanks to each other's consideration)
We clinked our glasses for the finale.
I think I was very fortunate.
I came to New York...
and went through a lot of special experiences.
There were many tough times as a foreign student,
but I also enjoyed my time working here.
The musical that I wrote as a writer...
is being shown to the audience in Broadway...
every single day.
It still feels like a dream.
It does feel like a movie.
I always think that...
I'm living a fortunate life.
(I might be a very lucky person.)
Let's congratulate each other one last time. Let's make a toast,
- cheers, and clink! - Cheers and clink!
That's what you said. Yes.
- Thanks for... - I should pack up.
Bringing all the trophies.
All right. Well, congratulations.
Congrats again!
Although the work continues.
I know.
So I'll see you at the theater.
- Yes. Bye, Will! - Bye.
(He cleans up after seeing Will off.)
Alexa.
Play "Perfect Places" by Lorde.
(Wiping)
(He finishes up quickly while listening to music.)
(Picking up)
(He continues to get to work.)
Oh, right. He has to get to work.
I want to continue to improve.
New York to me...
is part of my identity...
and a place of love and hate.
There's a certain energy that this place gives...
and that formed who I am now.
Living alone...
could feel lonely or exciting.
I want it to be a happy ending for me.
A life that I want to continue to develop.
That is the life that I live alone.
(My life that dreams of happiness and improvement)
Alexa.
Turn off all the lights.
(Certainly Happy Ending)
- That's impressive. - That's impressive.
That's truly impressive.
I feel a bit embarrassed.
- Why? - Why feel embarrassed?
- You haven't been writing. - No.
- To be honest, - You follow your own thoughts.
- Right. - after making a lot of webtoons,
I fell into this mannerism.
The passion that I had at start withered away.
But he wasn't like that.
He still cries after watching his own work.
Right. That was the most impressive part to me too.
Should I say that he looked bubbly?
I was jealous of how he looked innocent.
- That was what I felt. - Thank you.
I mentioned him before. Around 14 years ago,
I was with my NYX.
My ex that was in New York.
- Oh, "NYX." - I see.
I was with my NYX before.
When I first went,
we went to watch a musical in Times Square.
- What did you watch? - We watched "Chicago."
But I didn't speak any English at all.
Everyone else laughed, but I didn't understand why.
I remember when I laughed when the others laughed.
At the age of 27,
I imagined what it would be like...
to meet a person who makes these musicals.
I thought that to myself when I couldn't speak any English.
But as he's right here next to me,
- it feels really strange for me. - Right.
- It must feel strange. - Right.
I was really impressed.
What did you think, Kai?
(What did you think, Kai?)
Do you think you have achieved your goal?
(Joking)
If you don't feel satisfied,
- feel free to speak. - Right.
We should let him sing.
We should hold an audition.
It's true that I love Will and Hue's musical.
Right.
I'm not sure. It made me reflect upon myself as well.
After being an actor for around 20 years,
I naturally fell into a habitual routine.
- Right. - Right.
After watching Hue's day,
I wondered if I was really doing well.
I wondered if I didn't lose those pure and innocent moments.
I felt a bit of regret based on those thoughts.
I really enjoyed watching how he lived his life.
I am excited to see what he'll do in the future as well.
It's like you're writing a biography of him.
(It's like you're writing a biography of him.)
(Laughing)
Was it not a lecture?
- No. - No?
We should each get ready for an audition.
My gosh.
(Singing)
(I'll go through that audition now.)
(It's an honor.)
There will be an opportunity to meet each other.
- Right. - Definitely.
We hope that your life will become a happy ending.
We will root for you.
(We root for Hue Park's happy ending.)
(I Live Alone)
(A Miraculous Day)
(In the dark room, )
(Kian84 is fast asleep.)
- Where is this? - Is that his house or what?
- It's not his house. - It's not his house.
- It's not his house. - It is my house.
- That's your house? - Yes.
- I thought he was at a motel. - Same here.
(He's sleeping at home.)
(He starts wriggling at the sound of the alarm.)
It's that sound.
(Turning off the alarm)
(He gets up after letting out a sigh.)
What? It's 4am?
- Why get up so early? - Gosh.
I wake up from time to time at that time.
I had something planned at 5am that day.
I usually sleep at around that time.
If I train myself to wake up earlier,
there might be a time when I am able to spend longer days.
That was why I decided to wake up early.
- I feel tired. - That's really early though.
(He drags out his tired body out of the bed...)
(although it's really early.)
(Sighing)
(Opening)
(Coffee)
(Pouring the coffee into the tumbler)
(Taking a sip of morning coffee)
You must have coffee at that time.
It was hard to stay awake.
(He places the tumbler next to his things.)
(Loud blast)
- I blew my nose. - Your nose makes that sound?
(I blew my nose.)
(Taking a refreshing shower at 4:04am)
(Picking up)
He picked up his helmet.
(Putting on his hat)
(Kian84 is ready to leave.)
He doesn't look bright at all.
It's a time when it's hard to look bright.
(Shall I get going now?)
(Leaving at 4:19am)
Look at that. The sun isn't even out yet.
(The streets are silent without the sun out.)
(He starts the day at dawn on his own.)
Isn't that before the first bus is out?
Right. There are no buses at that time.
(Lifting)
Taxis must be taken during those times.
But why did you bring out your helmet?
I was going to use the shared bikes...
or electric scooters.
I only used taxis as it was really hot that day.
It is really hot.
I shouldn't have brought that out.
(Moving with the taxi while escaping from the heat)
(He dozes off while going across the bridge.)
I'll get off here.
Thank you.
- Gosh, it's hot. - Where is this?
(Han River Park?)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
It's my first time seeing Kian84.
It's my first time running with him.
What I had planned at 5am...
was to run by the Han River with others.
I didn't want to exercise in the morning...
as my body felt so heavy.
I didn't really bother to exercise in the morning,
but running out at night all the time could get boring too.
I decided to join a running group in the mornings if I could find one.
I got used to it after attending a few times.
Gosh, it's 5am.
- Never. - You're a great runner.
- All right. - Hello.
- Hello. Good morning. - Hello.
- It's him? - Good morning.
It's the legend.
(Hip-hop duo Jinusean's main rapper, Sean)
It's been a while since I saw him.
He's originally a singer. He's a rapper.
What kind of image does Sean have in the hip-hop scene?
He's someone whom I find it hard to even mention.
- He's a great senior, right? - He's older than Gaeko.
- I become like this right away. - Right.
- Right. - Right.
He must be the one that loves running the most in our country.
He's the archaeopteryx.
(Actor Park Bo Gum)
(Actor Im Si Wan)
- This crew is really famous. - Right.
(Record of 7 hours, 50 minutes, and 22 seconds)
This really brought me to tears.
(The Seanshine of runners, Sean)
Professional athletes...
call it the mileage...
and they run 400km to 500km every month on average.
- Sean runs even more than that. - How much does he run?
He runs up to 700km a month.
He runs more than professional athletes?
He runs more than athletes.
He wasn't able to compete in competitions during COVID-19.
- At his terrace at home, - His terrace.
He ran back and forth in the space that is less than 10m...
- and completed 42.5km. - He completed that distance.
Gosh!
There were several times when we ran together at night.
He told me to come out for a run in the morning.
There's that feeling when you have to wake up at boot camp.
There's a day you really don't want to get up.
The blanket feels so warm.
You want to stay inside your cocoon.
If Sean was forceful...
or scary, I wouldn't have gone.
But there's that feeling you get from a very nice person.
"Let's run together." This sort of feeling.
You don't want to disappoint people like him.
- Right. - Some people are like that.
They all come out with the same thing in mind.
(They all come out with the same thing in mind.)
They have been caught by the trap of his smile.
- It's hard to refuse him. - Right.
I understand.
Hello, Sean.
- Was the run okay? - Yes.
- Shouldn't you get some rest? - Well...
It hasn't been long since the run.
I have to prepare for Sydney again.
You got some rest the day after...
National Liberation Day of Korea, right?
- No. - What?
You ran the next day right away?
- Yes. - Gosh!
I ran the day before yesterday and yesterday as well.
(The Unknown Crew members gather up one by one.)
(Peeking)
They were all great runners.
Young Pyo's legs were still about to burst open.
- He was a national team member. - Gosh. He was a great talent.
The icon of hard work.
(Soccer legend, Lee Young Pyo)
The gold medalist of wrestling,
- Jung Ji Hyun. - Jung Ji Hyun?
- Right. - He was a gold medalist...
- in wrestling. - Right.
(The Asian wrestling king that went beyond weight classes)
I know him.
Coach Kwon Eun Ju. Korea's best female marathoner.
- Gosh. - It's her?
I definitely know her.
She's an athlete?
(Marathoner, Lee Yeoun Jin)
(Track and field athlete, Jang Ho June)
- Why is an athlete there? - Actor Go Han Min.
I heard that Yoon Se A was a great runner too.
- They're all the ones... - Workout YouTuber,
- that are known for their running. - Shim Eu Ddeum.
They're all from the top tier. Gosh.
It was a very intense crew.
I always go with a heart of learning.
- Welcome. - Hello.
(Welcome.)
Let's warm up in a larger area.
We'll start our exercise.
Please form a circle.
Let's do our exercise. Let's roll our ankles.
One, two, three.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three.
- One, two, three. - Four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four. - Two, two, three, four.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - Five, six, seven, eight.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - Why do you lack energy?
Three.
I couldn't get used to it because I don't run...
- in the morning. - One.
- How tiring. - My body wouldn't wake up.
That's all for the warmup.
We won't be able to run if we continue,
- so let's stop here. - Sounds good!
- Let's stop here. - Thank you.
All right.
Do we start right away?
Yes, we'll get moving now.
- We'll run 5km this way... - Yes.
- and come back to drink. - Okay.
Then we'll run 3km this way and come back.
If it's 15km, then...
It's 10km back and forth.
- It's 5km back and forth. - Oh, I see.
- It's 5km and 5km, so 10km. - Back and forth.
- Then it's 10km. - It's 10km.
It's 15km if we return from Seongsu Bridge.
That's 15km in total.
(The morning running course is 15km in total.)
Running 15km is long too.
- Running 15km is long too. - Of course it is.
It's in the morning.
- It doesn't end. - Running 15km is long too.
(He's run the full course before.)
Kian84 runs well.
Yes. New York City Marathon.
Let's get going.
Let's get moving.
(Nervous)
- It's really cool now. - It's gotten a lot cooler.
Right? It's cool now.
- Let's run in two lines. - Okay.
We'll start with a pace...
- of 6 minutes and 30 seconds. - Okay.
We got it today as well.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(Unknown Crew and Kian84 start running!)
We got it today as well.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(They set off while cheering for themselves.)
(Clearing his throat)
Show them.
Show them what you got.
At the pace...
- of 6 minutes and 30 seconds... - We'll run 2km.
- And then? - It'll be six minutes.
Six minutes.
I started running recently too,
and running at the pace of 6 minutes and 30 seconds...
is not that slow.
(They're to maintain the pace of 6 minutes per kilometer.)
Look at the sky.
Gosh, look to your left!
- It's pretty. - It's pretty.
Gosh, the sun is coming up.
- It's pretty. - That was the nice part.
Seeing the sun rise.
Time goes really fast, and so does the distance.
I think so too.
- If you run alone... - I can't run alone anymore.
I've gotten a disease of not being able to run alone.
- It's too fast! - Stop chattering!
Okay.
- Is it raining? - It's raining.
- It's raining. - It's so nice.
- Right? - I hope it pours.
It's raining?
It was really humid and hot.
I hate it when it rains because it gets icky.
But when I run, it's the best if it rains.
I think it's even better when the rain is heavy.
When I ran with the Yeouido crew,
- it rained heavily too. - That's right.
If you run in the rain,
you become a bit crazy.
You go a little crazy.
So I hoped it'd rain more.
(The rain pours down refreshingly.)
Doesn't it get slippery?
- It doesn't. - It doesn't?
- It's perfect when you run. - Let's go.
(The crew members are happy even when they get rained on.)
They look so happy.
They all look so bright.
(Gosh, it's refreshing.)
It's raining!
I didn't know,
- but he likes being in the rain. - I love running in the rain.
One, two, three!
It's raining!
Oh, my.
(Madness)
All right. We've run 2km so far.
(They finish running the 2km section in the rain.)
Go straight.
We'll run straight and go there.
There are fewer people, aren't there?
The group that runs slower...
runs separately in the back.
(They've run until Ichon-dong for 4km now.)
(Ichon, Oksu Station)
(It's 5:40am.)
(Running in the morning is a little hard.)
The halfway point is up ahead.
We'll turn right here and make a big round to the left.
- From here. - Halfway.
Turn. Okay.
One. Let's turn.
- Where is he going? - Where are you going, Kian84?
He has no sense of direction.
(He turned the opposite direction by himself.)
Let's go!
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Oh, hello!
- Hello. - Hello.
- Let's go, everyone! - If you run at your pace,
- Where did she go? - it puts you in a good mood.
They run so happily.
This is nice.
- Isn't it amazing? - It is.
It's beautiful.
Gosh, look at the back.
That was the nice part about running in the morning.
It's beautiful.
(The sky has completely brightened.)
You get to see the sun rise.
Let's go.
I loved the smell of early morning.
(He welcomes the morning with the sunrise while running.)
(They run straight while taking in the refreshing air.)
Two lines.
This is Jamsu Bridge.
(There's an uphill road ahead.)
Gosh.
- When you run uphill, - Bicycles, let's go!
- you slow down. - Yes.
(Slow down when running uphill.)
- With shorter strides. - Yes, run with shorter strides.
Don't look far ahead. Just look about 3m ahead.
(It gets faster downhill.)
How do you feel today?
I'm tired.
It's because you aren't fully recovered yet.
(Sean looks bright even when he runs while talking.)
(On the other hand, Kian84's smile completely disappeared.)
(As he runs at the pace of the crew members who run and smile...)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- We'll turn around up there. - Turn around.
They made it halfway.
Be careful.
(Ichon, Oksu Station)
Turn.
(Southern part of Jamsu Bridge)
All right.
(They don't slow down even after running half the course.)
(Then they face an uphill road again.)
(Gosh, I can't make it this way.)
Sean, isn't it too fast?
(Laughing)
Let's go!
The pacemaker should keep the pace well.
But Sean wasn't so good at keeping the pace.
- He's too fast, right? - Yes.
He keeps running fast if I don't stop him.
Doesn't he check the pace...
- while running? - He rarely did.
(Sean only looked forward and ran.)
Sean, it's 5 minutes per 1km.
- Gosh, sorry. - We've made it...
to 4 minutes and 55 seconds.
Sean keeps running faster.
He ran up until four-minute range when I didn't stop him.
Maybe I wasn't used to it.
Or maybe I was a little intimidated to run with good runners.
It was really tiring.
You run for the fun of giving pointers.
But when you're with people who run way better than you,
you get intimidated.
I thought I might be a burden to them.
I couldn't help but be self-conscious.
The pace is good.
(This is a good pace?)
I don't think you should be a pacemaker.
The coach should be a pacemaker.
(You're running too fast.)
I'm sorry. It's 5 minutes and 40 seconds.
It's 5 minutes and 40 seconds.
I'll keep it at six minutes.
Sean, it's 5 minutes and 45 seconds.
How come he's so fast?
- We need to go 15 seconds slower. - Okay.
- Sean. - Yes?
It's 5 minutes and 30 seconds now.
- Oh, okay. - All right.
Actually, it was 5 minutes and 25 seconds.
(As they ran with all their might, )
(they ran past the 10km point.)
- They run so well. - Gosh.
That's a lot.
(They ran past the 10km point.)
(Glancing over)
What's your heart rate now?
- It's 125bpm. - It's really low.
People who run well...
- have a low heart rate. - Of course.
It's pretty low considering the pace.
Mine is 140bpm.
- It's not bad if it's 140bpm. - Is it?
Ours would shoot up to 160bpm.
It changes depending on the weather,
and it depends on the time of the day too.
(Regardless of my heart rate, let's just look ahead and run.)
The view is amazing.
Gosh, it's amazing.
(The running crew burn up with the sun.)
It must be really tiring.
He runs so well, though.
(They've made past the 13km point.)
(Even if he falls behind for a second, )
(he keeps going forward with perseverance.)
Kian84. All right. Let's go.
We have 500m to go.
(Let's hang in there a little longer.)
Okay, we'll sprint after 50m.
(Let's go!)
Thirty, twenty.
Ten. Get ready.
Go.
We're ending it with the last interval run.
Interval?
- It kills you. The last one. - A sprint?
(Gathering every ounce of energy they have)
This really kills you.
(Running at full speed)
We raised our heart rate to the fullest...
- before ending the run. - That's right.
(Maximizing cardiovascular endurance with maximum heart rate)
- All right. - They run so well.
Slow down. Don't stop.
They ran that much that early in the morning?
It's unbelievable.
Because it was in the morning,
we ran slowly.
You can only burn 852 calories after running that much?
- Gosh. - It's so not time-effective, right?
- It's usually... - It's not even enough...
for a bowl of jjajangmyeon.
But you know it's the most effective exercise, right?
- Running is most effective. - Other workouts...
- That's true. - Really?
- Good work. - Great job.
You run so well.
You go separate ways after this, right?
Yes, we get dismissed after running.
Great job, director.
Let's go.
- Shall we run more? - Sorry?
- "Shall we run more?" - Let's go.
Well done, everyone.
(Among the lively veterans...)
(I'm dying.)
My goodness.
Thank you.
(The heartwarming crew members take care of the newbie.)
Great job.
I don't think I'll be able to go on with the day after this.
Me neither.
Gosh, running in the morning is tough.
So if you...
come out and run in the morning 2 or 3 times a week,
you'll get a lot more comfortable.
He's talking with a fairy-like smile.
- I'll come out a few more times. - Yes, keep coming.
It's... What time is it?
So your day starts now?
What do you do?
I take my kids to school,
then I get ready. For today,
there's an MOU signing...
for Seungil Hope Foundation, so I'm going there.
I have a YouTube shoot at 1pm.
After that, I'm going to volunteer work...
at a child rehab center at 7pm.
- Donation fairy. - I'm packed until the evening.
- How can one live like that? - I know.
- He's amazing. - He's incredible.
Don't you take a nap?
I don't.
He only sleeps four hours a day.
Goodness.
(Hesitating)
Are you happy?
It's a sincere question.
That's the question I wanted to ask.
Everyone must've been curious.
I was a little out of it. That's why I asked him that.
Well done.
- Aren't you fooling yourself? - No.
"I'm happy."
I still have this habit.
I'd criticize a lot as a webtoonist.
"He must be..."
"thinking otherwise deep inside."
I was curious about him...
because he does so many good deeds.
He's like a hero...
who'd appear in textbooks.
- I know. - How can one live like that?
If you eat only organic food every day,
- you want to have instant food too. - That's right.
- Wouldn't he want that too? - Since he's a human too.
- Aren't you fooling yourself? - No.
"I'm happy."
- I'm really happy. - "I'm having fun."
- If I were really fooling myself, - Yes.
There'd be a point...
- where I give up. - That's true.
He's consistent too.
- How about 5km more? - Let's go.
- For real? - Gosh.
Go ahead.
- See you again. - Have fun.
- Yes. - Let's go!
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Gosh, they're amazing.
- He's out of energy. - Gosh, it's hot.
Let's stretch.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's start stretching. - All right.
Grab your head and pull down.
- One, two. - Oh, the post-run stretch.
- Three. One, two... - It's a healthy way to start a day.
And seven.
Seven, eight.
We'll wrap up here.
- Great job. - At 4am...
- Good job. - They're amazing.
- Great job. - Great job.
- Look at him. He's exhausted. - Great job.
Great job.
(Screaming)
The new member of Unknown Crew.
- What? - A new member?
- He's done for. - Is he an official member now?
The new member of Unknown Crew.
- I'll come back next year. - Right?
- I have something to give you. - What?
We got you headphones and a T-shirt.
Can I take them next time?
He's trying to leave as soon as he can.
He's hurrying off.
- I'll come back for the interview. - All right.
- Great job. - All right.
- Bye. - Good job.
Great job.
(End of running, 8:30am)
- He must be tired. - He must be tired.
I think I'll have to...
take a nap for three hours in that state.
I know.
(Kian84 trudges somewhere.)
Gosh, it's hot.
(Jamwon Swimming Pool)
- What? - A swimming pool?
- It's popular these days. - It is.
Thank you.
- Hello. - Hello.
- One adult, please. - Okay. Please insert your card.
I saw this place...
every time I ran in the evening.
It's steaming hot after a run during summer.
I've always wanted to go into the pool.
Since I was soaked in sweat anyway,
I thought I might as well just go.
- It's pretty. - Gosh.
It's really colorful.
It's nice, right?
There weren't that many people that day.
Because it was in the morning.
- Oh, right. It's in the morning. - That's right.
My shirt stinks because I sweated.
(I should wash up first.)
(Taking off the socks that were kept in the shoes for 15km)
(Getting up)
- Gosh. - Gosh, that must be refreshing.
- Was it cold water? - Water gushes out there.
Goodness.
- Gosh! - Goodness.
Gosh, the crack wash.
(Feeling liberated from the run)
(Time to scrub away dirt from the morning run)
- Oh, is it soap? - That's body wash.
It looks really refreshing.
Running makes you happier.
Running for an hour and a half was torturing, to be honest.
But after that,
drinks taste about eight times better.
I feel about four times happier when I shower.
Gosh, how refreshing.
(He takes his clothes...)
(and goes to the changing room.)
(He strides forward in his swimsuit.)
I should have ramyeon.
They sell ramyeon too?
(Han River ramyeon and sundae)
- Oh, my. That's nice. - That's nice.
- I sweated too much, - Again?
- so I craved it so much. - It looks so good.
Han River ramyeon is delicious.
(Happy)
I want to eat ramyeon.
- It looks amazing. - Gosh, seriously.
(Taking a bite of sundae while waiting)
- That's what you call happiness. - It must be good.
(Taking a sip of the pickled radish juice)
It must be sour and nice.
Gosh, he drinks it like it's soda.
So he drinks that too?
(Pouring)
(What is that?)
- What is that? - It's sour and nice.
It's like tom yum kung.
- Sour... - It's sour and salty.
(He's done making tom yum kung ramyeon.)
(Shall I have the first meal of the day?)
He's the only one eating.
That's the nice thing about mornings.
It'd have been too crowded at night.
(First meal of the day, 9:30am)
Take a big bite.
- Gosh, that must be good. - Goodness.
It's amazing.
(This time, he has a bite with pickled radish.)
Because I sweated a lot,
I craved salt so much.
It was almost like...
my cells absorbing salt.
It was like my skin absorbing salt.
They sucked in the salt by themselves.
They absorbed it straight.
(Absorbing salt right away)
It almost drove me crazy.
(Salt hits his body fast.)
Gosh, how come I never get sick of ramyeon?
(That was a satisfying first meal.)
You punk. Why are you in there?
(I'm full.)
We'll open the pool now.
(He's ready with goggles.)
Gosh, people practice swimming there.
It's quite deep.
- Hello. - Hello.
Is it divided into different levels?
- I don't think so. - Oh, really?
Can you swim to the other end?
Is it 25m?
- I think it's 50m. - It's 50m?
- Yes. - It's not easy to swim 50m.
- It was quite long. - Of course.
- Swim to the other end? - They're quite good.
Just like running every day,
there are people who come to swim every day.
They can swim all they want outdoors.
(It's finally his turn.)
(He relaxedly sets off in freestyle.)
- Where is he going? - What?
- Gosh. - He's going over the lane.
- What is he doing? - Oh, gosh.
He might bump into them. No.
Why is he swimming like that?
(He swims forward diagonally.)
Goodness.
Gosh.
(I almost bumped into him.)
He's going diagonally again.
Gosh, he's going to bump into him.
I kept swimming toward the left.
I learned to swim from that person.
At a community culture center,
there are old ladies who are like penguins.
There are old women who swim like this underwater.
- They're really good. - There's a team of old ladies.
You can go straight if you keep looking at the floor...
because there are lines drawn.
- But there were no lines there. - Oh, there were no lines.
The ladies from the center would be upset here...
because there are no lines.
Oh, right. There are straight lines...
- on the swimming pool floors. - Right.
They didn't have one.
(Panting)
(Thinking)
(He suddenly dives.)
(Shall I try the butterfly stroke since it's a miracle morning?)
(Jang Woo does the standard butterfly stroke.)
- Jang Woo is good. - He's really good.
That form is really cool.
(Drowning)
Throw him a rope.
- Lifeguard! - Someone...
- Lifeguard! - Save him!
It was okay until the third stroke.
- Save him. - Someone save him.
You become a bit crazy.
You go a little crazy.
- You're too tensed up. - Yes.
Your legs are tensed up.
(He doesn't move forward at all.)
How come he's still in the same place?
Isn't he drowning?
(He struggled for a long while.)
That's how people swim.
(Flapping)
- You should just rest. - It must be really tiring.
- Yes. - I think he'll pass out...
during the day.
Does this make sense? He's swimming after running.
Gosh.
I wasn't made of iron or something.
It's not like you're a marine.
(Shaking)
It must be really tiring.
(It feels like he aged 15 years more.)
(It's too tiring.)
(He strides forward without even drying himself.)
(Dropping)
What kind of day is this?
(It's only 10:30am.)
Because I run every day, only my arms and legs are tanned.
My torso is pale.
- Right. Your torso is pale. - It was a sore sight.
(Lying down)
I can't believe someone can do that in the middle of Seoul.
It's so nice.
If I tan it for 20 minutes...
(I think it'll be nice if I tan it for 20 minutes.)
I think it'll be nice.
(Kian84 finally gets to rest in earnest.)
I should flip over.
(His body feels heavy.)
Shouldn't someone report him?
I saw this in "Detective Conan."
There's evidence.
Look at the side. There's a trace of water.
- The fact that there's water... - Isn't that a dying message?
It could be a dying message.
It is a dying message. The butt print tells something.
He was lying straight when he was killed,
but the culprit flipped him over.
No, it means someone with a pretty butt is the culprit.
(Dead men tell no tales.)
(The truth sinks into mystery.)
Oh, my. Ants are swarming around.
(Ants swarm around him in no time.)
- Why would ants swarm around? - What?
(Kian84 doesn't even have the energy to chase away the ants.)
(Groaning)
- Gosh, ants are swarming around. - It's a crime scene.
What is this?
(Worn out)
I always work out before bed,
so my day ended after a workout.
But after working out early in the morning,
I was given a day to myself.
Two.
(He started the day with a miracle morning.)
That's a long day.
Shouldn't he take a nap when he gets home?
- He should. - I should.
He can't help but fall asleep.
Those who don't run in the morning.
I got nine more hours to myself.
Running in the morning is magnificent.
After enduring the pain,
I was given nine more hours.
I'm exhausted.
You aged a little.
I feel like I'm dying.
Even with blood-shot eyes, I earned nine more hours.
My eyes are as red as rabbits, but I earned nine hours.
You can sleep after you die.
But you can live nine more hours with blood-shot eyes.
A miracle morning.
It must be Sean.
(Shaking)
(I'll call you later, Sean.)
(Gosh, these ants.)
Gosh, the ants.
(11am, Neverending Miracle)
What did you do afterward?
I went to my office and painted for two hours.
Then I slept afterward at home.
Your day became shorter.
Didn't your day shorten?
(Next story)
(It really is big.)
Who'd install this at home?
(What is this huge thing hanging on the wall?)
(The masterpiece of the century, Na Rae's broom-to-be)
(Reborn as a huge Naphrodite)
(The bigger it is, )
(the bigger her self-love is.)
(I love myself.)
(Another way to care for myself)
(Dressing up and going out)
(We love you, Na Rae!)
(My neighborhood loves me just as much as I love myself.)
(Where did she arrive at?)
(Filled with people she's glad to see)
(It's the bar Na Rae frequents.)
(Light conversations exchanged with her neighbors)
(They become one regardless of their nationalities.)
(A place where she shares her love)
(She carefully shares her sincerity...)
(by picking up the tab at a place she cherishes.)
(Drunk in Me, Drunk in This Place)
(Deficiency heat?)
(Me, who was skinny, had pain, and had cold hands?)
(Weak)
(I...)
(have changed.)
(Forget my past.)
(Charming man)
(A trip the charming man is taking)
(Jae Hyeon came to his friend's surfing shop.)
(His friend of 16 years...)
(and her husband)
(And their cute son, Si On)
(They head to the sea together to surf.)
(Nervous)
(Today's surfing instructor)
(Si On gives a demonstration.)
(Getting up)
(A V sign)
(Giving it a try, following Si On's lead)
I think I could do better.
(I'll show you my changed self.)
(I Will Show You My Changed Self)